<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Digital Marketing on W Digital Agency | AI Automation &amp; Digital Marketing Agency for Southeast Asia</title>
    <link>http://localhost:50255/categories/digital-marketing/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Digital Marketing on W Digital Agency | AI Automation &amp; Digital Marketing Agency for Southeast Asia</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-uk</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 08:00:00 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:50255/categories/digital-marketing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>CPAHK Webinar Highlights Digital Marketing&#39;s Impact on Beauty and Cosmetics Industry</title>
      <link>http://localhost:50255/portfolios/cpahk-webinar-digital-talk-on-dtspp/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 08:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:50255/portfolios/cpahk-webinar-digital-talk-on-dtspp/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Hong Kong – On December 19, 2024, &lt;a href=&#34;https://www.cosmetic.org.hk/&#34;&gt;the Cosmetic &amp;amp; Perfumery Association of Hong Kong&lt;/a&gt; (CPAHK) hosted a successful webinar that attracted over 20 merchants from the beauty and cosmetics sector. The session focused on the pivotal role of digital marketing in facilitating digital transformation for small-to-medium enterprises (SMEs) in Hong Kong.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img loading=&#34;lazy&#34; src=&#34;https://www.wingleung.me/wp-content/uploads/2025/01/CPAHK-digital-talk.jpg&#34; alt=&#34;Webinar on digital transformation with financial support by DTSPP, a Hong Kong Cyberport fund&#34;  /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;about-digital-transformation-support-pilot-program-dtspp&#34;&gt;About Digital Transformation Support Pilot Program, DTSPP&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The webinar emphasized critical areas such as &lt;strong&gt;e-commerce&lt;/strong&gt;, &lt;strong&gt;website marketing&lt;/strong&gt;, and &lt;strong&gt;digital advertising&lt;/strong&gt;, providing valuable insights into how these elements can enhance business operations and customer engagement. Participants were introduced to the &lt;strong&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://dtspp.cyberport.hk&#34;&gt;Digital Transformation Support Pilot Programme&lt;/a&gt; (DTSPP)&lt;/strong&gt;, an initiative by HK Cyberport designed to assist SMEs in adopting ready-to-use digital solutions. This program features a &lt;strong&gt;1:1 matching funding scheme&lt;/strong&gt;, allowing participants to receive financial support to improve their operational efficiency and competitiveness within the industry.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Are You Planning to Build Your Own Website? Here Are Our Suggestions for CMS in 2024</title>
      <link>http://localhost:50255/buidling-website-cms-suggestions-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2024 08:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:50255/buidling-website-cms-suggestions-2024/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;With the ever-evolving digital landscape, choosing the right Content Management System (CMS) is crucial. In 2024, there are numerous options available, each with unique benefits tailored to different needs. Here’s a comprehensive guide to help you identify your objectives, estimate your budget, and choose the best CMS for your project.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;identify-your-objectives&#34;&gt;Identify Your Objectives&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Before diving into the technical aspects, it’s essential to clarify &lt;strong&gt;what your website will be used for&lt;/strong&gt;. Consider the following questions:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
