<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Website Marketing on W Digital Agency | AI Automation &amp; Digital Marketing Agency for Southeast Asia</title>
    <link>http://localhost:50255/tags/website-marketing/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Website Marketing on W Digital Agency | AI Automation &amp; Digital Marketing Agency for Southeast Asia</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-uk</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2024 08:00:00 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:50255/tags/website-marketing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Are You Planning to Build Your Own Website? Here Are Our Suggestions for CMS in 2024</title>
      <link>http://localhost:50255/buidling-website-cms-suggestions-2024/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Nov 2024 08:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:50255/buidling-website-cms-suggestions-2024/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;With the ever-evolving digital landscape, choosing the right Content Management System (CMS) is crucial. In 2024, there are numerous options available, each with unique benefits tailored to different needs. Here’s a comprehensive guide to help you identify your objectives, estimate your budget, and choose the best CMS for your project.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;identify-your-objectives&#34;&gt;Identify Your Objectives&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Before diving into the technical aspects, it’s essential to clarify &lt;strong&gt;what your website will be used for&lt;/strong&gt;. Consider the following questions:&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Case Study: AC Home - SEO and SEM Strategies for Lead Generation of a Air Con Cleaning and Repairing Company in Hong Kong</title>
      <link>http://localhost:50255/portfolios/achomehk/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Oct 2024 00:10:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:50255/portfolios/achomehk/</guid>
      <description>Explore how AC Home improved lead generation by shifting focus from competitive keywords to high-intent phrases like &amp;lsquo;Repairing Air Con&amp;rsquo; and &amp;lsquo;Fixing Air Con Leaking Water.&amp;rsquo;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tip From Agency: The Importance of Owning and Holding Your Website Domain Name: Benefits of Direct Ownership</title>
      <link>http://localhost:50255/the-importance-of-owning-your-website-domain-name-for-digital-marketing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:50255/the-importance-of-owning-your-website-domain-name-for-digital-marketing/</guid>
      <description>One crucial element of this online presence is a domain name, which serves as your unique address on the internet.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Academy of Fencing Hong Kong - Google Ads Consultation</title>
      <link>http://localhost:50255/portfolios/academy-fencing-hk-portfolio/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2023 10:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:50255/portfolios/academy-fencing-hk-portfolio/</guid>
      <description>Academy of Fencing (Hong Kong), a local fencing school looks for more leads during the summer period, as this is their first time of using Google Ads and search engine marketing. The lead quality is much better than on social media platforms.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
